-=伊甸园美剧 http://sfile.ydy.com=- 时间轴微调:-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组 时间轴组=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业途径
反恐24小时 第二季 第24集 web-dl版本时间轴调节:dizhang
前集剧情摘要
以後你可能不能跟我联络
- 为什麽? - 我得搞定查裴尔
所以他们怀疑到我了
- 他们很快会带我走 - 我要跟谁求援?
蜜雪儿会用远程存取 尽力来协助你
- 你被捕了 蜜雪儿在哪里? - 我知道她在哪里
抓到了  她已被逮捕
琴? 哈罗
- 奶是谁? - 我是凯蒂华纳
奶父亲要我来接奶
我爸怎麽会叫一个 他刚认识的人来接我?
他信任我
我们越早离开 奶就越早能跟奶父亲相聚
司法部长说你要找我
- 他们怎麽说的? - 你被卸职了
这个证据 被彼得金斯利所利用
我要你尽全力调查这个人
- 怎麽帮你? - 只剩最後一招 交出金斯利
他这人极端危险 而且你没办法接近他
说的对 是奶不是我去
金斯利不知道修特已死
就说奶要交出修特 就会引起他的兴趣
我要我们谈话的录音带
我会用修特做交换
洛城体育馆 18号出入口 30分钟
- 反恐小组有什麽支援? - 什麽都没有
以下是发生在早上 7点至8点的事
还好吗?
快呀
车子发不动 我们下车
安全带卡住了
派默夫人 请你帮我
请不要这样
抱歉 我得顾我自己 等我可以了我会叫救护车
- 不可以这样 - 别无选择
你很棒 可惜你对善恶太分明 就像大卫一样
- 这世界是很复杂的 - 是很简单的
一场战争快要开始了 你是唯一可以帮我阻止此事的人
- 不为总统吗? - 他离弃了我
25年的生活 建立的家庭 他却离弃了我
他们最後还是会知道是你的
核弹本来是不该引爆的
事情本来不该是这样的
我知道 我相信你 但你可以阻止此事的
帮我捉到金斯利 你丈夫会重新出任总统
那会是你的功劳
派默夫人  求求你
你要我怎麽做?
置物箱里面有小刀 帮我割开
进来吧
这样好多了 比较简单 我们必须想办法说明
- 麦克 我有事跟你说 - 我五分钟後下来
麦克
很重要
失陪一下
什麽事?
这是金斯利的档案 几分钟前调出来的
杰克鲍尔 认为一切都是他主使的
他在约六小时前打电话 给一名叫做乔纳森华的军人
那军人就是 珊瑚蛇突袭队的人
明显的是他杀了自己人
我知道他是谁
轰炸机刚通过最後的哨站 一小时内就会到达目的地
主攻击目标是军事单位
但那是个位於住宅区域 的指挥中心
不论我们武器有多精确 都会产生间接伤害
会伤到平民
- 无可避免吗? - 没办法
那我们就只好这麽办
我是查裴尔
- 我是麦克纳维 - 有什麽事  长官?
我知道有人对有关塞浦路斯 录音的真假有所争议
我们的鉴定 与朗利那边的是一样的
那鲍尔还在寻找 伪造录音的证据吗?
对 他未经授权
我要你协助他的调查
- 长官  我根本不知道他在哪里 - 那就找到他
为何要我这麽做? 我们不是该准备作战吗?
还没有  30分钟内给我 杰克所找到的结果
- 可是长官... - 这是命令
你知道我的联络方式 用这条专线回报给我
- 我要过一小时才上飞机 - 为何要延迟?
核弹引爆地点不对 所以有些额外的工作
不必担心什麽  我希望
不会的 我不想烦你了
你讲
我还得处理修特
修特是唯一的证人了
- 你不是说已经处理掉他了 - 我找不到他
我会处理的 别担心
你们俩  坐下
你不必对付蜜雪儿 她只是听命行事
- 我自己来讲 - 我要你们坐下
我要你们帮我 联络杰克鲍尔
我明白了 杰克上面有人支持 现在你有压力了
- 到底办不办得到? - 是怎麽一回事?
或许杰克找到的 证据是真的
- 所以我们是对的 - 不  你们差点害死我
竟敢攻击我
我告诉你
你不要对付我们 我们就会帮你
少来了  雷恩 所有人都会建议你这麽做的
- 好吧 - 白纸黑字
好的  写下来 快帮我找到鲍尔
- 不找人支援吗? - 我现在不是听命於反恐小组
- 对他们来说我并不存在 - 所以我们只能靠自己
完全靠自己
- 你还好吗?需要帮助吗? - 他受伤了
- 可以送我们到医院去吗? - 好的  当然
- 派默夫人  你来开车 - 什麽意思?
- 抱歉  我们要用你的车 - 别紧张  拿去  开走吧
谢谢
已经好了  长官
- 我姓华纳  嗨  卡丽你好 - 嗨  凯蒂
- 你一定就是杰克的女儿 - 我爸在哪里?
他还在外面 等一下 我去告诉查裴尔你们来了
- 让我来处理 - 你不是被看管了
已经释放了
琴  我知道出了什麽事 你还好吧?
应该没事  我想看我爸爸 我要知道他是否有事
他现在不在 要几个小时才会回来
- 他知道我在这儿吗? - 他若来电我们会告诉他
- 杰克说我们一到达就要打给他 - 现在电话接不通
卡丽会带你们到後面休息 我马上就过来
不会有事的
华纳小姐?
不知你是否知道 你父亲被释放後有回来
为什麽?
他要在你妹妹被带走前 和她讲几句话
玛莉被带到这边吗?
你欺骗了我?
你杀了理沙?
还想杀你姐姐?
你真的想引爆核弹 害死上千万人?
告诉我为什麽? 因为我必须了解
告诉我你是被逼的 你被洗脑了 你受到威胁
告诉我你不知道 自己在做什麽
一定是有理由的
没有理由  爸爸
我不能接受
我也不能
当时她举起枪对着我要扣扳机 我看着她的眼睛
相信我  爸爸
她不会回答你的
她无法做到 那是我们无法理解的原因
爸...
好了 我们走
凯蒂
你以为在外面会安全
其实不然
- 我是东尼 - 你复职了吗?
琴已经到这里了
- 她很安全 - 谢谢老天  别告诉她我的事
- 就说我很快会回来 - 我会的
- 我是雷恩  我们得谈谈 - 你这浑蛋
是你阻止救援的直升机
- 害修特死掉  这要你负责 - 现在不一样了
你有完全的支持 告诉我现在的任务
我要去见金斯利 在洛城体育馆18号出入口
派默夫人会让他确认 事情与那三个国家无关
想办法撑到後援到达 很快就会到了
没时间了 现在就要和金斯利会面了
你需要後援
你想帮忙 就找出金斯利 与派默夫人的声纹做确认
好了
- 还要与白宫现场语音传输 - 通到总统吗?
好吧  线路不要断掉
- 收到  我们要进体育馆了 - 赶快派迅雷小组到那里去
停在那里
在这里等我
过来
我帮你装窃听器
脱掉外套
这是无线发讯器
不会被他们知道 也不会被发现
- 这太疯狂了  不能单独行动 - 别无选择
金斯利没有见到 修特不会走的
这就是我们的优势
讲话
我好怕
可以用
总统先生 我现在推翻自己 从一开始反对延迟开打的立场
因为现在很有机会取得 伪造塞浦路斯录音的证据
我们都知道 第二波带了核弹入境
也知道这一切 都是那三个国家赞助的
虽然现在还没有细节 但我刚发现一个线索
第二波与一个 叫金斯利的男子有关联
他是谁?
他控制  海油田
是油田的人主使核弹的吗?
鲍尔相信他能让金斯利讲出实话 他要现场语音连线
轰炸机再20分钟就要轰炸了
鲍尔马上要和他会面了
这是现场语音声纹传送
这是纪录上的对照语音档
这可以证明说话的人 的确是雪莉派默
- 确认了 - 下面这个是金斯利?
- 你们收得到吗? - 很清楚
- 多久後援会到? - 11分钟
- 太久了  现在就要进去了 - 等一下
不行 我们已经迟到10分钟 普雷斯科特准备好了吗?
东尼已经接上白宫 正在设定现场语音传送
好  那一切就搞定了
你那边如何?派默夫人?
万一金斯利要杀我呢?
没看到修特之前 他不会动手的
但是一旦他发现 修特不在我们手上...
我会掩护你的
你这种状况 让我不能安心
我可能不会活着走出来
我不想骗你 那是有可能的
我这麽做是为了大卫 你很清楚  对不对?
对
你会告诉他吗? 万一出了什麽事情
我会的  派默夫人 你过去吧
- 麦克 - 是的  长官
传输连线已经准备好了 希望这不是浪费时间
相信我 总统先生 我也一样
怎麽了 麦克?
总统与我都觉得这件事 应该也让你叁与
普雷斯科特与司法部长 都会一起听现场语音传送
- 听什麽? - 对付彼得金斯利的秘密行动
他主使核弹之事 并以塞浦路斯录音栽赃
鲍尔找到金斯利
但是要与金斯利对话的 不是鲍尔
只要能让他认罪 也没什麽差别
有什麽事?麦克
是雪莉要与金斯利对谈
我不懂
看来几个月前 金斯利找了她串通
她也叁与其中
雪莉为金斯利工作?
看似如此  长官
引爆核弹并挑起战争? 不会的
目前不清楚她了解多少 或牵涉有多深
希望她能引出金斯利认罪
现在雪莉与鲍尔配合 要把金斯利引出来吗?
她要冒相当的危险
史考特 我没有指示前别动作
- 我们需要修特 - 了解
- 修特在哪里? - 他很安全
他在哪里?
你骗我  你根本 就计画要引爆核弹
你利用了我与罗杰斯坦顿
是的  没错
现在我被你牵连 也与核弹牵连 我要求自保
- 那是你的问题 - 现在是你的了
我若出事 你也别想见到修特
- 你别想骗我 - 你也别当我是呆子
- 找到符合金斯利的声音 - 雷恩  听到没
不交出修特你就别想走
这不是让你来决定的
等我离开到安全之处 我才会打电话告诉你他在哪里
我不会让你知道我的行踪
- 没有我们要听的 - 她会问出来的
- 录音带的问题要解决 - 都在这里
我们之间所有的通话录音
不 我要全部 包括塞浦路斯的
为什麽? 那与你无关
要保障
只要一开打 政府也不会发表此证据的
修特是唯一能伤害我们的人
- 因为录音是他伪造的 - 对
- 证据都有了  我们走 - 让白宫先确认
- 她必须赶快抽身 - 满意了吗?
反恐小组要知道 这样的证据是否充分
有确认过这声音真的是现场 并通过鉴定?
是的  长官
那就够了
等我降落  我再打电话给你
你在唬我 修特根本就不在你手上
- 是真的 - 不  是假的
史考特  杀了她
干掉她
雪莉  快跑
快点
雪莉  快离开  快
杰克鲍尔
你今天给我很多麻烦了
你不会交出修特  对不对?
轰炸机离目标只有三分钟
开始探戈一号第六一程序
目标出现  武器锁定
要开始攻击吗?
可以发射了吗?
我们已经待命中
取消攻击
取消  取消
什麽意思?金斯利死了? 怎麽会这样?
我警告过你不要用他
我们用了他  但失败了
没关系 只要战争一开始就好了
- 不会开始了 - 为什麽?
总统已经知道录音的事 取消攻击了
不会打仗了  麦克斯
我们得用另一种方法来
- 你在讲什麽? - 你会知道的
今天就会开始
是我  开始吧
内阁取消之前的决议
我已经请特勤组 恢复对您的服务
您现在是美国总统
我明白了
我也已经提出辞呈 即刻生效
所有投票反对您的内阁 也已经都同意辞职
吉姆
各位先生  女士...
今天我们几乎 要发动无谓的战争
大家对核弹爆炸之事 感到情绪化是可以理解的
但身为领袖 必须比常人更具耐心
我们所要采取的行动
应该在所有证据查明後方可执行
必须透过最严苛的求证
你们草率的隔离我 只会降低求证的水准
这是很大的错误
但是我相信 以後绝不会再发生这种错误
所以我不接受你们的辞呈
我们今天要赶快安定国家
你们每一位都担负着 重要的任务
总统先生...
我不知道该说什麽
不必说了
还有很多工作要做
就这样子
- 珍妮  准备开记者会 - 几时?
尽快 我要公开一切
我要直接面对人民 他们需要我给的保障
是的  长官
麦克  我要谢谢你 在最後关头找反恐小组的人
不客气  总统先生
你本应该 与我共同坚持到底
这是我对你的期望
所以我才对你交付重任
现在你可以卸职了 即刻生效
好的  总统先生
谢谢你  长官 我不能占功劳
乔治梅森所带领的人员 都很出色
我知道 谢谢  长官
是总局局长范恩
他对今天我们的表现大感高兴 不知要从哪里开始讲
太棒了
怎麽了  朋友?
是...
是这样的
你若不开除我
就请马上离开我的位置
这位置是你的
轮班的人到了 他们都得到交接资料了
我想去接我哥回家
今天的少数人 创造了很大的成绩
你也是其中之一
你下了难以抉择的决定 而且反抗过我  但你是对的
谢谢
赶快回去休息吧
明天见
- 我得检查袋子里的东西 - 我是凯蒂华纳  这是琴鲍尔
借过
- 嗨  亲爱的 - 爸爸
一切都会好的
我知道
我爱你
我也爱你
爸  我要照顾你
我要强烈的要求你们
不可对现在或可能会听到的 不实传闻与谣言加以渲染
一旦全部事实查明後 我会亲自对各位发布
在此之前 大家都要知道自己 很安全 也不会再有任何危险
今天大家可以充分表现出的 爱国精神就是好好的过日子
我呼 大家 回到工作岗位 回到学校去
因为我们所享受的自由 每天所得到的自由
就是我们用以战胜敌人的一切 也是让我们坚强的理由
天佑美国
天佑吾民  谢谢
非常谢谢 主保佑大家
谢谢
谢谢 见到你们真好
总统先生
嗨
抱歉 总统先生
谢谢
总统先生
- 嗨 - 谢谢
- 主保佑你 - 谢谢
- 喂 - 完成了
谢谢
总统先生?
总统倒下了 快找医护人员  救命
快搜查那个人
- 总统先生? - 检查武器
总统先生? 不会有事的
需要救护车  快点
-=伊甸园美剧 http://sfile.ydy.com=- 时间轴微调:-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组 时间轴组=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业途径
24 S02E24 Day 2 7_00 AM - 8_00 AM (VO+STFR&EN)
You may not be able to contact me.
- Why? - Chappelle became a problem.
I had to take him out of play and they're onto me.
- They'll take me out soon. - Who do I contact if I need help?
Michelle is setting up an off-site station.
- You're under arrest. Where's Dessler? - I can find her.
Affirmative, Central. She's in custody.
Kim? Hello?
- Who are you? - I'm Kate Warner.
Your father sent me to come get you.
Why would my dad send someone he'd just met to come get me?
He trusts me.
The sooner we leave, the sooner you and your dad can be together.
The Attorney General said you'd want me for your counsel.
- What have they told you? - You've been removed from office.
The evidence was manipulated by a man named Peter Kingsley.
I need you to find out all you can about him.
- What happens now? - We got one last play. Deliver Kingsley.
He's far too dangerous, and you'll never get close to him.
You're right. I won't, but you will.
Kingsley doesn't know Hewitt's been killed.
If you say you can deliver him, that should get his attention.
I want the tapes that you made of our conversation.
I'll give you Alex Hewitt in return.
All right. LA Coliseum, gate 18, 30 minutes.
- What support will you get from CTU? - As of now, none. Ow!
Jack? Jack!
- You OK? - Yeah.
Come on.
Damn it. The car won't start. We gotta get out of here.
My seat belt's jammed.
Mrs Palmer, I'm gonna need your help.
Mrs Palmer, please don't do this.
I'm sorry, but I have to take care of myself.
When I'm free I'll call an ambulance.
- You can't do this! - I don't have a choice.
You're a very impressive man,
but you see everything as either good or bad, just like David.
- The world is so much more complicated. - No, it's simple.
There's a war about to start and you're the only person who can help me stop it.
- What about the president? - He turned away from me.
After 25 years of building a life together, a family, he turned me away.
Eventually they will connect you to this conspiracy.
That bomb was never supposed to go off.
None of this was supposed to happen this way.
I know. I believe you. You can put an end to it now.
If you help me get Kingsley, your husband will get his presidency back.
That will be because of you.
Mrs Palmer, please.
God damn it!
What do you want me to do?
There's a knife in the glove box. Help cut me out.
Come on in.
This is much better. It's simpler. We gotta be able to explain this thing.
- I need to talk to you, Mike. - I'll be down in five minutes.
Mike.
It's important.
Excuse me.
What is it?
It's a file on Peter Kingsley. They pulled it up a few minutes ago.
Peter Kingsley, the man Jack Bauer thinks is behind the bomb.
There's a record of phone calls he made, as recently as six hours ago,
to a soldier named Jonathan Wallace.
Wallace was a member of the Coral Snake brigade.
He apparently killed his own men.
I know who Wallace is.
The planes have passed over their final checkpoint
and will reach their targets within the hour.
Our primary targets are all military,
but one includes a command-and-control centre inside a residential area.
As smart as our weapons have become, there may be some collateral damage.
You mean civilian casualties.
Yes, sir.
- There's no way to avoid these? - I'm afraid not.
Then it's something we're just gonna have to live with.
Ryan Chappelle.
- Ryan, this is Mike Novick. - How can I help you, sir?
I know there's been some confusion today about the veracity of the Cyprus audio.
Not really. Our teams came to the same conclusion as Langley.
Do you know if Bauer's still trying to find evidence that the recording was fabricated?
Yes, but he's operating outside our authority.
I want you to assist his investigation.
- Sir, I don't even know where he is. - Then find him.
I'm not sure why you're asking me to do this.
I was told we're at war and to proceed accordingly.
We're not at war yet. You have 30 minutes to report back to me
the findings of Bauer and your efforts.
- But sir... - That's a direct order, Ryan.
You have my channel. Call me back on this line. That's all.
- I'll be on the plane in an hour. - Why the delay?
The bomb detonating in the wrong location created a little extra work.
Nothing to worry about, I hope.
Not at all. I won't bore you with the details.
Bore me.
I still have to take care of Alex Hewitt.
Hewitt is the only one who can bring this whole thing down.
- You told me you'd have him by now. - I wasn't able to find him.
But I'm taking care of it. Don't worry.
Sit down, both of you.
You don't need Michelle here. She was acting under my orders.
- I can defend myself, Tony. - I said sit down.
I need you to get me in contact with Jack Bauer.
Oh, I see. Jack got some support above you and now you're being squeezed, right?
Can you do it or not?
What's goin' on?
Bauer's evidence might actually have some relevance.
- Which means we were right. - No. You damn near put me in a coma.
That's assault.
I'll tell you what. You drop the charges against us...
and we'll help you.
Come on, Ryan. You of all people know that's your best move.
- Fine. - In writing.
All right, in writing. Just get me in touch with Bauer.
- Shouldn't we call for help? - I'm not working under CTU's authority.
- To them I don't exist. - So we're out on our own.
Completely.
- Are you all right? You need some help? - He got hurt.
- Can you get us to a hospital? - Uh, yeah, yeah, sure.
- Mrs Palmer, you need to drive. - What do you mean?
- Sorry, but we need your car. - Hey, easy, all right? Go ahead, take it.
Thank you.
They're ready, sir.
- Miss Warner. Hi. Carrie Turner. - Hi. Kate.
- You must be Jack's daughter Kim. - Where's my dad?
He's still in the field. Wait here. I'll tell Ryan Chappelle you're here.
- I'll handle this. - I thought you were in custody.
I was released.
Kim, I heard what happened to you. Are you all right?
Yeah, I guess so. Look, I just wanna see my dad and make sure he's OK.
No, he's not here right now. He won't be back for a couple of hours.
- Does he know I'm here? - No. We'll tell him when he phones in.
- Jack insisted we call as soon as we get here. - He's just not reachable now.
I'll have Carrie take you back and get you situated. I'll be there in a minute.
Hey.
It's gonna be OK.
OK.
Miss Warner?
I don't know if you're aware of this but...
your father came back here after we released him.
Why?
He wanted to talk to your sister before she was taken away.
- They brought Marie back here? - Yeah.
You lied to me?
You killed Reza?
You tried to kill your own sister?
You were willing to set off a nuclear bomb in a city with ten million people?
You tell me why. Because I need to understand.
Tell me that they forced you to do it, that they brainwashed you, that they threatened you.
You can tell me that you didn't know what you were doin'.
There must be a reason.
There is no reason, Dad.
I can't accept that.
I couldn't either.
Until I looked into her eyes and she pointed a gun at me and started to pull the trigger.
Trust me, Dad.
She's not gonna give you any answers.
She can't. At least, nothing that we could ever understand.
Dad...
Come on. Let's go.
Kate.
You think you'll be safe out there.
You won't be.
- Jack, it's Tony. - Tony, you back in play?
Yeah. Jack, Kim's here at CTU.
- She's safe. - Thank God. Don't tell her what's going on.
- Just say I'll be back as soon as I can. - I will.
- Jack, this is Ryan. We need to talk. - You son of a bitch.
You stopped that chopper picking up me and Hewitt.
- Hewitt's dead. I hold you responsible. - Listen, things have changed.
You got full support. Give me your mission profile.
I've set up a meeting with Kingsley.
We're gonna meet him at the LA Coliseum, gate 18.
Mrs Palmer will wear a wire and make him confirm
that the three countries had nothing to do with the nuke.
Stand down until you get some support. Our people will be there soon.
We don't have time. Kingsley's expecting the meet to go down now.
You need backup.
If you wanna help me, get me voice prints of Kingsley and Mrs Palmer for authentication.
Done.
- And a live audio feed to the White House. - You want an audience with the president.
Yes.
All right. Keep the line clear.
- Copy. We're pulling into the Coliseum now. - We need to get a SWAT team to his location.
Pull over there.
Wait here for me.
Come on.
Let's get you wired.
Take your jacket off your shoulder.
This is a wireless transmitter.
They won't know to look for it. They won't be able to trace it.
- This is crazy. We shouldn't do this alone. - We don't have another choice.
Remember, Kingsley doesn't want to leave here without Hewitt.
That's gotta be to our advantage.
OK, say something.
I'm scared.
OK, it's working.
- Yes, Mike. - Mr President,
I am against any delay in our military actions. I have been from the start.
But there is a good chance we'll receive evidence soon the Cyprus recording is false.
We know Second Wave brought the nuke into the country
and we know they're sponsored by these three countries. What am I missing?
I don't have all the details, but I just learned about a possible link
between Second Wave and a man named Peter Kingsley.
Who is he?
He's apparently part of a consortium of oil interests with contracts in the Caspian Sea.
An oil consortium's behind the nuke?
Bauer believes he can get a confession from Kingsley. He's set up a live audio feed.
Our bombers are due to drop their payloads in less than 20 minutes.
Bauer's meeting Kingsley any minute.
This is the live voice print.
And this is the voice file we have on record
which will prove that it is, in fact, Sherry Palmer.
- It's confirmed. - The one below is Kingsley?
- Yeah. - Are you guys getting this?
- We're good here. - How far out is our backup?
- They're 11 minutes out. - That's too long. We've gotta go now.
- Just wait. - We can't.
We're already ten minutes past the meeting time. Is Prescott ready?
Tony's on with the White House. They're setting up a live audio feed.
OK, good. We are set to go.
How are you doing, Mrs Palmer?
What's to prevent Kingsley from shooting me?
He won't do anything until he gets Hewitt.
But the moment he realises we don't have Hewitt...
I'll be covering your back.
That's not very comforting considering the condition you're in.
I may not make it out of this.
I'm not gonna lie to you, Mrs Palmer. That's a possibility.
I'm doing this for David. You know that, don't you?
Yes.
Will you tell him that? In case something happens.
I'll take care of it, Mrs Palmer. You've gotta go now.
- Mike. - Yes, sir.
We just finished setting up the feed. I hope this isn't gonna be a waste of our time.
Believe me, Mr President, so do I.
What's going on, Mike?
The president and I thought you should be part of this.
Along with Prescott and the Attorney General, we will be listening to a live feed.
- Of what? - A sting operation against Peter Kingsley.
It appears he was the architect of today's bombing
and the delivery of the Cyprus audio.
- Bauer found Kingsley. - Yes.
But... it won't be Bauer who'll be talking to Kingsley.
What difference does it make as long as we get him to incriminate himself?
What is it, Mike?
It's Sherry who'll be talking to Kingsley.
I don't understand.
It seems that Kingsley recruited her some months ago.
She was part of this.
Sherry was working with this man, Kingsley?
It appears that way, sir.
To detonate a nuclear bomb and start a war?
No.
It's unclear how much she knew, or how deep she was in it.
We just have to hope she can extract a confession from Kingsley.
So now Sherry is working with Jack Bauer to bring down Kingsley?
Yes. And at considerable risk to herself.
Scott, don't do anything until I tell you to.
- We need Hewitt. - Understood.
- Where's Hewitt? - He's safe.
Where is he?
You lied to me. You wanted this bomb to go off all along.
You used Roger Stanton and you used me.
Yes, I did.
Well, now I'm tied to you, and the nuclear detonation. I want safe haven.
- That's your problem. - Well, I just made it yours.
Because you won't see Hewitt until I'm safe.
- Don't horse trade with me. - Don't insult my intelligence.
- We got a match on Kingsley's voice. - Ryan, you got it.
You're not going anywhere till I have Hewitt.
That doesn't work for me.
I'll call you on this line to give you Hewitt's location after I'm safely away.
You don't need to know where I'm going.
- We're not getting what we need here. - She'll get it for you.
- Now there's the matter of the recordings. - They're right here.
Every phone conversation between you and me.
No. I want all of them, including Cyprus.
Why Cyprus? You had nothing to do with that.
- Insurance. - Insurance?
Once the country goes to war, the government will never let that be exposed.
Hewitt is the only one who can hurt us.
- Because he forged the Cyprus recording. - Right.
- You got your proof. Let me go ahead. - Get it confirmed from the White House.
- She can't stay much longer. - Are you satisfied?
CTU wants to know if that's enough to prove it.
Have you confirmed this is live and the voices have been authenticated?
Yes, sir.
- So that's it. - Yes.
When I land... I'll call you.
Hm.
You're bluff in'. You don't have Hewitt, do you?
- Oh, yes, I do. - No, you don't.
Scott, take her out.
Kill her.
Run, Sherry!
Come on. Come on.
Mrs Palmer, get out of here. Go!
Jack Bauer.
You've caused me a lot of trouble today, Jack.
You're not gonna give me Hewitt, are you?
Our bombers are three minutes from the targets.
Initiating sequence six one tango one.
Target in view. Weapons lock.
Are we go for a strike?
Are we go for a launch?
We are awaiting command.
Abort the attack.
Abort, abort.
What do you mean, Kingsley's dead? How could that happen?
I warned you not to use him.
So we did use him and he failed.
But it won't matter. Once the war starts we'll be OK.
- It isn't going to start. - Why's that?
The president found out about the Cyprus recording and called off the attack.
There isn't going to be any war, Max.
Well... we're going to have to do this another way.
- Another way? What are you talking about? - You'll find out.
It'll start today.
It's me. Go ahead.
The cabinet has annulled its earlier action.
I have instructed the Secret Service to resume its charge of serving you
as President of the United States.
I see.
I've also tendered my resignation, effective immediately,
and those members of the cabinet who voted against you have also agreed to resign.
Jim.
Gentlemen, ladies...
we came dangerously close to war today.
That all of us reacted emotionally to the nuclear detonation is understandable.
But leaders are required to have patience beyond human limits.
The kind of action we nearly took should only be exercised
after all other avenues have been exhausted.
After the strictest standard of proof has been met.
By casting me aside so quickly, you effectively lowered those standards.
And that was a profound mistake.
It was not, however, a mistake you're likely to make again.
Therefore I do not accept your resignations.
We have a nation to heal today.
And all of you play a vital role in that healing process.
Mr President...
I don't know what to say.
There's nothing to say.
We have work to do.
That'll be all.
- Jenny, set up a press conference. - When?
As soon as you can. And I want it public.
I want to speak to the people directly. They deserve my assurance.
Yes, sir.
Mike, I wanna thank you again for calling CTU in the 11th hour.
Of course, Mr President.
But you should have been with me to the end.
That's what I expected of you.
That's why I appointed you.
I'm relieving you of your post, effective immediately.
Yes, Mr President.
Thank you, sir. I can't take all the credit myself.
It's a great team George Mason put together here.
Yes, I will. Thank you, sir.
Tony. That was District Director Vaughn.
He's so happy with what we did here today he doesn't know where to start.
That's great.
So... what's up, my friend?
Well, um...
it's like this.
Either fire me...
or get out of my chair.
The chair's all yours.
- Hey. - Hey.
The new shift is here. They've been brought up to speed.
I was thinking I'd get my brother and go home.
Michelle, um...
there's a handful of people who made a big difference today.
You're one of'em.
You made some tough choices and went up against me. You were right.
Thanks.
So, um... why don't you go home and get some rest?
Michelle.
See you tomorrow.
- I'll need to see the contents of your bag. - I'm Kate Warner and this is Kim Bauer.
Excuse me.
- Hey, honey. - Daddy.
It's gonna be all right.
I know.
I love you.
I love you too.
Dad? I'm gonna take care of you.
I urge you in the strongest terms
not to indulge any rumours or theories that you may have heard, or may soon hear.
Once the facts are known, I will present them to you myself.
Until then, know that we are all safe and that we will continue to be safe.
The most patriotic thing that we can all do today is to keep living our lives.
So I urge you all, go back to work, go back to school.
Because the freedom we enjoy, the freedom that we earn every day,
is the very thing that will defeat our enemies and keep us strong.
God bless America.
God bless us all. Thank you.
Thank you very much. God bless you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Good to see you.
Thank you.
Mr President!
Hi.
Excuse me, Mr President.
Thank you.
Mr President.
- Hi. - Thank you.
- God bless you. - Thank you.
- Yes. - It's done.
Thank you.
Mr President?
The president's down! We need medical assistance. Help!
Mr President? It'll be all right, sir.
We need an ambulance! Help!